[{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980247075,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"15","question":"What is the greatest accomplishment of your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":13927,"timeElapsed":44228},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980254177,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"15","question":"What is the greatest accomplishment of your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":7099,"timeElapsed":51329},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980264801,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"15","question":"What is the greatest accomplishment of your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":10622,"timeElapsed":61954},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980273141,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"15","question":"What is the greatest accomplishment of your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":8337,"timeElapsed":70293},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980276140,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"15","question":"What is the greatest accomplishment of your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":2997,"timeElapsed":73293},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980278737,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"15","question":"What is the greatest accomplishment of your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2594,"timeElapsed":75890},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980280878,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"15","question":"What is the greatest accomplishment of your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2139,"timeElapsed":78031},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980284027,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"15","question":"What is the greatest accomplishment of your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":3147,"timeElapsed":81180},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980289444,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"15","question":"What is the greatest accomplishment of your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":5415,"timeElapsed":86597},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980293951,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":2485,"timeElapsed":91104},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980301240,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":7286,"timeElapsed":98393},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980305252,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":4010,"timeElapsed":102405},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980306536,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":1282,"timeElapsed":103689},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980308497,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":1959,"timeElapsed":105650},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980311767,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":3268,"timeElapsed":108920},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980314174,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":2404,"timeElapsed":111326},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980317856,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":3680,"timeElapsed":115009},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980320333,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":2476,"timeElapsed":117486},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980341455,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":20150,"timeElapsed":138608},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980342764,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":1306,"timeElapsed":139916},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980345003,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":2237,"timeElapsed":142155},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980346189,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":1185,"timeElapsed":143342},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980348396,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":2205,"timeElapsed":145549},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980350905,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2506,"timeElapsed":148058},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980353057,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":2150,"timeElapsed":150210},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980360387,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":7328,"timeElapsed":157540},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980361683,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":1294,"timeElapsed":158836},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980367138,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"109","question":"What traits or skills do you most admire in others?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4711,"timeElapsed":164290},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980371756,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"109","question":"What traits or skills do you most admire in others?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":4617,"timeElapsed":168909},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980374216,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"109","question":"What traits or skills do you most admire in others?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":2457,"timeElapsed":171369},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980375339,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"109","question":"What traits or skills do you most admire in others?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":1121,"timeElapsed":172492},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980377935,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"109","question":"What traits or skills do you most admire in others?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":2595,"timeElapsed":175088},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980380743,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"109","question":"What traits or skills do you most admire in others?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":2806,"timeElapsed":177896},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980382219,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"109","question":"What traits or skills do you most admire in others?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":1474,"timeElapsed":179372},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980384104,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"109","question":"What traits or skills do you most admire in others?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":1882,"timeElapsed":181257},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980385237,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"109","question":"What traits or skills do you most admire in others?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":1131,"timeElapsed":182389},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980395032,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":8999,"timeElapsed":192185},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980396544,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":1510,"timeElapsed":193697},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980398786,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":2241,"timeElapsed":195939},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980400598,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":1811,"timeElapsed":197751},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980406473,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":5873,"timeElapsed":203626},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980408889,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2415,"timeElapsed":206042},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980410355,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":1463,"timeElapsed":207507},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980417143,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":6786,"timeElapsed":214296},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980419090,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"192","question":"What’s the best pair of shoes you own or have owned? What makes them awesome?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":1945,"timeElapsed":216243},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980426754,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"223","question":"What is the most unusual food you’ve ever eaten? Describe where and when you last had this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":6672,"timeElapsed":223907},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980427893,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"223","question":"What is the most unusual food you’ve ever eaten? Describe where and when you last had this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":1136,"timeElapsed":225045},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980429172,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"223","question":"What is the most unusual food you’ve ever eaten? Describe where and when you last had this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":1277,"timeElapsed":226325},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980430703,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"223","question":"What is the most unusual food you’ve ever eaten? Describe where and when you last had this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":1529,"timeElapsed":227856},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980433161,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"223","question":"What is the most unusual food you’ve ever eaten? Describe where and when you last had this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":2456,"timeElapsed":230314},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980434846,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"223","question":"What is the most unusual food you’ve ever eaten? Describe where and when you last had this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":1684,"timeElapsed":231999},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980436697,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"223","question":"What is the most unusual food you’ve ever eaten? Describe where and when you last had this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":1849,"timeElapsed":233849},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980439202,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"223","question":"What is the most unusual food you’ve ever eaten? Describe where and when you last had this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":2504,"timeElapsed":236355},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980440426,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"223","question":"What is the most unusual food you’ve ever eaten? Describe where and when you last had this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":1222,"timeElapsed":237579},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980447312,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":6131,"timeElapsed":244465},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980448768,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":1455,"timeElapsed":245921},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980450010,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":1241,"timeElapsed":247163},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980451920,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":1907,"timeElapsed":249073},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980454037,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":98,"rt":2116,"timeElapsed":251190},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980457414,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":3375,"timeElapsed":254567},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980459016,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1600,"timeElapsed":256169},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980461422,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2404,"timeElapsed":258575},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980462585,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":1161,"timeElapsed":259738},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980468890,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"154","question":"Who is your favorite actor or actress? Describe a favorite scene in which this person has acted.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":5219,"timeElapsed":266043},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980469834,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"154","question":"Who is your favorite actor or actress? Describe a favorite scene in which this person has acted.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":942,"timeElapsed":266987},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980470810,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"154","question":"Who is your favorite actor or actress? Describe a favorite scene in which this person has acted.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":974,"timeElapsed":267963},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980471949,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"154","question":"Who is your favorite actor or actress? Describe a favorite scene in which this person has acted.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":1137,"timeElapsed":269102},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980473907,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"154","question":"Who is your favorite actor or actress? Describe a favorite scene in which this person has acted.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":1956,"timeElapsed":271060},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980475866,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"154","question":"Who is your favorite actor or actress? Describe a favorite scene in which this person has acted.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":1957,"timeElapsed":273019},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980477372,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"154","question":"Who is your favorite actor or actress? Describe a favorite scene in which this person has acted.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":1504,"timeElapsed":274525},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980482911,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Who is your favorite actor or actress? Describe a favorite scene in which this person has acted.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5537,"timeElapsed":280064},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980487477,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"154","question":"Who is your favorite actor or actress? Describe a favorite scene in which this person has acted.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":4564,"timeElapsed":284630},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980488740,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"154","question":"Who is your favorite actor or actress? Describe a favorite scene in which this person has acted.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":1262,"timeElapsed":285893},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980494847,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"196","question":"What was your favorite board game growing up or currently?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":5117,"timeElapsed":292000},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980497996,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"196","question":"What was your favorite board game growing up or currently?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":3148,"timeElapsed":295149},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980499068,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"196","question":"What was your favorite board game growing up or currently?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":1070,"timeElapsed":296221},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980500181,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"196","question":"What was your favorite board game growing up or currently?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":1111,"timeElapsed":297334},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980502749,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"196","question":"What was your favorite board game growing up or currently?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2566,"timeElapsed":299901},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980504620,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"196","question":"What was your favorite board game growing up or currently?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":1869,"timeElapsed":301773},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980507445,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"196","question":"What was your favorite board game growing up or currently?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":2823,"timeElapsed":304598},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980509772,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"196","question":"What was your favorite board game growing up or currently?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":2326,"timeElapsed":306925},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980524511,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What was your favorite board game growing up or currently?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":14737,"timeElapsed":321664},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980526834,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"196","question":"What was your favorite board game growing up or currently?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":2321,"timeElapsed":323987},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980531805,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":4295,"timeElapsed":328958},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980533080,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":1273,"timeElapsed":330232},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980534523,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":1442,"timeElapsed":331676},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980535934,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":1409,"timeElapsed":333087},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980537355,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1419,"timeElapsed":334508},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980539293,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":1936,"timeElapsed":336445},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980543607,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4312,"timeElapsed":340760},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980545429,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":1821,"timeElapsed":342582},{"subjectID":"7r0v72hqgt","prolificID":"6751138797ff44e336a37cba","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b260dbb47d1eef2a9d04","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980547847,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":2416,"timeElapsed":345000}]